Once a boy and a girl met at tuition.   At
first, they were complete strangers.  Then we became
friends, then best friends.
Initially we used to meet only in tuition classes.
Then after tuition, we started going out for a walk.
Friendship was slowly turning into love
and classes were sometimes even bunked.  The
families of both of them did not
know anything and they both were dreaming of their future together.  The
boy was
very fond of travelling.  Now that she had become a girlfriend from a friend, the
boy asked her if she would like to
visit Shimla.  Now the girl was
very keen to go out for a walk.  But when she did not even study in the Quiet school,
what would she tell her family
?  I want to go to Shimla with my boyfriend.  There was an
argument between the two.  The boy
put forward his point, the girl put forward her point.
Both of their points were valid, but they could
not go to Shimla together.  It took
him from 2016 to 2026 just to see this board.
Apart from God, both of them did
not trust anyone in the whole world.
Because when even his own people had rejected him, it was
God who gave
him everything - opportunity to earn money, car, house
and today he has come driving the car he earned himself.  The
gates of Himachal are standing in front to welcome them.  The
last 10 years
came to mind like a flashback.  This is the life the girl
always wanted.  Why do only boys have to
take all the responsibilities?  I drive
, my partner sleeps comfortably, and when he
drives, I sleep comfortably.  Well,
life was not so easy
for both of them.  There were many ups and downs, fights
, anger but neither did he
listen to those four people in the world nor to
his family members and in 2023 they both became one.
I have talked so much to
you all today.  My throat went dry.   I
drink sugarcane juice.  So you guys
think and tell me in the comments whether you
know that boy and girl.